Guide to the Nell Irvin Painter Papers, 1793-2021 and undated, bulk 1876-2007 RL.00990
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession (2022-0027), 1950s-2021
  - Whiteness symposium, Racial Imaginary Institute, 2018 June 30 (Box 315)
  - Emerson College, 2019 May 12 (Box 315)
  - Honorary degree from Emerson College, 2019 May 12 (Oversize-folder 1)
  - Personal documents, 1985-2002 (Box 315)
  - Floppy disks, 1996-2002 (Box 315, Disk RL00990-FL3-0001 - RL00990-FL3-0006)
    6 floppy disks with content related to lectures, texts, and a beauty prospectus.
  - Loose material 1, 2018-2019 (Box 315)
    Mostly correspondence with a few essay drafts.
  - Loose material 2, 2019 (Box 315)
    Mostly correspondence, notes, and essay drafts.
  - Loose material 3, 2016-2019 (Box 315)
    Mostly correspondence, notes, and photographs.
  - Loose material 4, 2019-2021 (Box 315)
    Mostly correspondence.
  - The New York Times Book Review, 2019 April 28 (Oversize-folder 1)